

- +959-979-877-629
- **9** Yangon, Myanmar
- www.shaungbhone.com

BHONE MYINT ZAW

Full Stack Web Developer

Driven 4-year experienced web developer with a passion for crafting visually appealing and user-friendly websites. Seeking a challenging role where I can utilize and contribute my coding skills, creativity, and problem-solving abilities to deliver cuttingedge web solutions that meet client needs and enhance user experiences.

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React and Vue.is.
- Node.js, Laravel.
- TALL stack and PEST.
- Nuxt, Next
- Typescript
- MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.

- Python, PHP.
- Apache, Nginx.
- Git.
- · Docker.
- GraphQL.
- Amazon Web Services
 (AWS) and Google Cloud
 Platform (GCP).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Senior Full Stack Developer/ Team Lead

Mint | May 2022 - present

- Designing and developing high-quality software solutions: designing, developing, testing, and deploying software applications using various programming languages, frameworks, and tools.
- Leading development projects: working closely with project managers and collaborating with other team members.
- Mentoring junior developers: mentoring and coaching them to develop their skills and grow as developers.
- Providing technical guidance to architects, developers, and quality assurance professionals.
- Maintaining code quality: ensuring that the codebase is maintained at a high level of quality, including enforcing coding standards, performing code reviews, and ensuring that best practices are followed.
- Collaborating with other teams, such as product management,
 UX/UI design, and quality assurance.
- Participating in software architecture design, providing insights into technical feasibility and recommending the best architectural solutions.
- Identifying and resolving technical issues, bugs, and performance problems in software applications.

Junior Developer

Digital Dots | Mar 2020 - June 2022

- Developing and maintaining WordPress websites, including installing and configuring WordPress, creating and customizing themes, and installing and configuring plugins.
- Collaborating with senior developers to ensure that WordPress websites are developed according to best practices and meet project requirements.
- Designing and implementing website functionality, including creating custom post types, custom taxonomies, and custom fields.
- Staying up-to-date with new WordPress features
- Providing technical support
- Testing and quality assurance

Freelance Full Stack Developer

Upwork | May 2022 - present

 Communicating with international clients for their specific requirements

Managing the projects to getting done within project timelines

Part-time Web Developer

Deegix | 3 Days

• Maintaining drupal websites for Deegix

• Managing the projects to getting done within project timelines

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Geology (2012 - 2017)

Pyay University, West Bago

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCIES

English Burmese Japanese

COURSES AND TRAINING

Myanmar Links, Yangon

Certificate of Professional Advanced Web Development

Laracasts, Online

Learning programming skills to the next level, through expert screencasts on PHP, Laravel, Vue, and so much more.

Hackerrank

Certificate of React Basic

PROJECT HISTORY

SHAUNG BHONE

TECHNOLOGIES

- Laravel
- Livewire
- Pest
- Postgres
- Alpine.js
- AWS

TECHNOLOGIES

- Nodejs
- Typescript
- Graphql
- AWS Amplify
- AWS Lambda
- AWS

TECHNOLOGIES

- Laravel
- Inertia
- Typescript
- Tailwindcss
- MailChimp API
- Digital Ocean

TECHNOLOGIES

- Laravel
- Vuejs
- Postgres
- Bootstrap
- Voyager Admin

TECHNOLOGIES

- Wordpress
- Elementor
- Mysql
- Bootstrap

TECHNOLOGIES

- Wordpress
- Elementor
- Mysql
- Bootstrap

DIGIFYME www.digify-me.com

For Digifyme, Developing the learning management system as a platform for teachers, students, and other users. I have managed and implemented the project as a team leads for the entire project. Digifyme website is developed by two senior full-stack developers. One is responsible for developing the learning platform and the admin panel, forum, and the rest items are developed by me. For the Admin panel, filament admin is utilized and AWS services are used for the hosting part.

KEYPERSONS key-persons.jp

Keyperson is the project for business representatives' communication. We have developed a program of event creation for business representatives and also built the functions for checking the event as a user. The Keyperson project is part of the aidma holding's project.

MINTASIA www.mintasia.co

Mint website is the static portfolio website for digital agency. For mint website, we have developed it as clean as possible as per brand guidelines. Within a very short period, our team managed to develop the efficient website.

MSME www.msmemm.org

Msme website is the project of Myanmar SME's Development Centre. The founder of our agency made me lead this project, developed with Laravel as I am very passionate with it. Authentication and Online forum parts are the main parts that I've developed and the whole project's architecture was set up.

DENKO MYANMAR www.denkomyanmar.com

Denko Myanmar is one of the leading companies in Myanmar. This project is to develop a static portfolio website. Upgrading the outdated versions and maintaining the website, resolving errors are the main tasks of me.

PRONITI TRAVEL www.pronititravel.com

Proniti Travel is one of the well-known travel agencies in Myanmar. The project is to develop a portfolio website with full information. I was responsible for maintaining the website. Upgrading the versions of PHP and WordPress is the main task for me while resolving the errors and bugs which lead me to gain a lot of experience to be a good developer

PSMC www.psmc.org.au **TECHNOLOGIES** Wordpress PSMC (Panditarama Sydney Meditation Centre) is the website of • Elementor meditation Centre at Sydney. The objective for this project is to build Mysql the informative website. It was developed for PSMC as CSR project by • Bootstrap Digital Dots. ACAE www.acaemyanmar.com **TECHNOLOGIES** Wordpress Australian International Preschool & Primary School in Yangon for Mysql Myanmar Students. This project is to create the clean and informative Bootstrap website. It is the very first project when I started working in tech industry. I had to start with this project as a coding test by the founder. I was working on all pages of the website as per the design provided by UI Designers.